export const data = [{
  front: 'か',
  back: 'KA'
}, {
  front: 'あ',
  back: 'A'
}, {
  front: 'さ',
  back: 'SA'
}, {
  front: 'た',
  back: 'TA'
}];
export const cards = [{
  front: 'か',
  back: 'KA',
  id: 1,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'あ',
  back: 'A',
  id: 2,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'さ',
  back: 'SA',
  id: 3,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'た',
  back: 'TA',
  id: 4,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'な',
  back: 'NA',
  id: 5,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'は',
  back: 'HA',
  id: 6,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'ま',
  back: 'MA',
  id: 7,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'や',
  back: 'YA',
  id: 8,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'か',
  back: 'KA',
  id: 9,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'ら',
  back: 'RA',
  id: 10,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'わ',
  back: 'WA',
  id: 11,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'い',
  back: 'I',
  id: 12,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'き',
  back: 'KI',
  id: 13,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'し',
  back: 'SHI',
  id: 14,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'ち',
  back: 'CHI',
  id: 15,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'に',
  back: 'NI',
  id: 16,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'ひ',
  back: 'HI',
  id: 17,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'み',
  back: 'MI',
  id: 18,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'り',
  back: 'RI',
  id: 19,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'う',
  back: 'U',
  id: 20,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'く',
  back: 'KU',
  id: 21,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'す',
  back: 'SU',
  id: 22,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'つ',
  back: 'TSU',
  id: 23,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'ぬ',
  back: 'NU',
  id: 24,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'ふ',
  back: 'FU',
  id: 25,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'む',
  back: 'MU',
  id: 26,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'ゆ',
  back: 'YU',
  id: 27,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'る',
  back: 'RU',
  id: 28,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'え',
  back: 'E',
  id: 29,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'け',
  back: 'KE',
  id: 30,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'せ',
  back: 'SE',
  id: 31,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'て',
  back: 'TE',
  id: 32,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'ね',
  back: 'NE',
  id: 33,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'へ',
  back: 'HE',
  id: 34,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'め',
  back: 'ME',
  id: 35,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'れ',
  back: 'RE',
  id: 36,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'お',
  back: 'O',
  id: 37,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'こ',
  back: 'KO',
  id: 38,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'そ',
  back: 'SO',
  id: 39,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'と',
  back: 'TO',
  id: 40,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'の',
  back: 'NO',
  id: 41,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'ほ',
  back: 'HO',
  id: 42,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'も',
  back: 'MO',
  id: 43,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'よ',
  back: 'YO',
  id: 44,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'ろ',
  back: 'RO',
  id: 45,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'を',
  back: 'WO',
  id: 46,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'ん',
  back: 'N',
  id: 47,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'カ',
  back: 'KA',
  id: 48,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'サ',
  back: 'SA',
  id: 49,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'タ',
  back: 'TA',
  id: 50,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'ナ',
  back: 'NA',
  id: 51,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'ハ',
  back: 'HA',
  id: 52,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'マ',
  back: 'MA',
  id: 53,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'ヤ',
  back: 'YA',
  id: 54,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'ラ',
  back: 'RA',
  id: 55,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'ワ',
  back: 'WA',
  id: 56,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'キ',
  back: 'KI',
  id: 57,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'シ',
  back: 'SHI',
  id: 58,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'チ',
  back: 'CHI',
  id: 59,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'ニ',
  back: 'NI',
  id: 60,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'ヒ',
  back: 'HI',
  id: 61,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'ミ',
  back: 'MI',
  id: 62,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'リ',
  back: 'RI',
  id: 63,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'ク',
  back: 'KU',
  id: 64,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'ス',
  back: 'SU',
  id: 65,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'ツ',
  back: 'TSU',
  id: 66,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'ヌ',
  back: 'NU',
  id: 67,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'フ',
  back: 'FU',
  id: 68,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'ム',
  back: 'MU',
  id: 69,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'ユ',
  back: 'YU',
  id: 70,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'ル',
  back: 'RU',
  id: 71,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'ケ',
  back: 'KE',
  id: 72,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'セ',
  back: 'SE',
  id: 73,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'テ',
  back: 'TE',
  id: 74,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'ネ',
  back: 'NE',
  id: 75,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'ヘ',
  back: 'HE',
  id: 76,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'メ',
  back: 'ME',
  id: 77,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'レ',
  back: 'RE',
  id: 78,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'コ',
  back: 'KO',
  id: 79,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'ソ',
  back: 'SO',
  id: 80,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'ト',
  back: 'TO',
  id: 81,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'ノ',
  back: 'NO',
  id: 82,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'ホ',
  back: 'HO',
  id: 83,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'モ',
  back: 'MO',
  id: 84,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'ヨ',
  back: 'YO',
  id: 85,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'ロ',
  back: 'RO',
  id: 86,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'ヲ',
  back: 'WO',
  id: 87,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'ン',
  back: 'N',
  id: 88,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'ア',
  back: 'A',
  id: 89,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'イ',
  back: 'I',
  id: 90,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'ウ',
  back: 'U',
  id: 91,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'エ',
  back: 'E',
  id: 92,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'オ',
  back: 'O',
  id: 93,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'gojūon']
}, {
  front: 'が',
  back: 'GA',
  id: 94,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'ざ',
  back: 'ZA',
  id: 95,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'だ',
  back: 'DA',
  id: 96,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'ば',
  back: 'BA',
  id: 97,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'ぱ',
  back: 'PA',
  id: 98,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'ぎ',
  back: 'GI',
  id: 99,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'じ',
  back: 'JI',
  id: 100,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'ぢ',
  back: 'DI',
  id: 101,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'び',
  back: 'BI',
  id: 102,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'ぴ',
  back: 'PI',
  id: 103,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'ぐ',
  back: 'GU',
  id: 104,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'ず',
  back: 'ZU',
  id: 105,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'づ',
  back: 'DU',
  id: 106,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'ぶ',
  back: 'BU',
  id: 107,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'ぷ',
  back: 'PU',
  id: 108,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'げ',
  back: 'GE',
  id: 109,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'ぜ',
  back: 'ZE',
  id: 110,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'で',
  back: 'DE',
  id: 111,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'べ',
  back: 'BE',
  id: 112,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'ぺ',
  back: 'PE',
  id: 113,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'ご',
  back: 'GO',
  id: 114,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'ぞ',
  back: 'ZO',
  id: 115,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'ど',
  back: 'DO',
  id: 116,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'ぼ',
  back: 'BO',
  id: 117,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'ぽ',
  back: 'PO',
  id: 118,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'ガ',
  back: 'GA',
  id: 119,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'ザ',
  back: 'ZA',
  id: 120,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'ダ',
  back: 'DA',
  id: 121,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'バ',
  back: 'BA',
  id: 122,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'パ',
  back: 'PA',
  id: 123,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'ギ',
  back: 'GI',
  id: 124,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'ジ',
  back: 'JI',
  id: 125,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'ヂ',
  back: 'DI',
  id: 126,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'ビ',
  back: 'BI',
  id: 127,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'ピ',
  back: 'PI',
  id: 128,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'グ',
  back: 'GU',
  id: 129,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'ズ',
  back: 'ZU',
  id: 130,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'ヅ',
  back: 'DU',
  id: 131,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'ブ',
  back: 'BU',
  id: 132,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'プ',
  back: 'PU',
  id: 133,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'ゲ',
  back: 'GE',
  id: 134,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'ゼ',
  back: 'ZE',
  id: 135,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'デ',
  back: 'DE',
  id: 136,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'ベ',
  back: 'BE',
  id: 137,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'ペ',
  back: 'PE',
  id: 138,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'ゴ',
  back: 'GO',
  id: 139,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'ゾ',
  back: 'ZO',
  id: 140,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'ド',
  back: 'DO',
  id: 141,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'ボ',
  back: 'BO',
  id: 142,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'ポ',
  back: 'PO',
  id: 143,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'きゃ',
  back: 'KYA',
  id: 144,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'yōon']
}, {
  front: 'しゃ',
  back: 'SHA',
  id: 145,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'yōon']
}, {
  front: 'ちゃ',
  back: 'CHA',
  id: 146,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'yōon']
}, {
  front: 'にゃ',
  back: 'NYA',
  id: 147,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'yōon']
}, {
  front: 'ひゃ',
  back: 'HYA',
  id: 148,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'yōon']
}, {
  front: 'みゃ',
  back: 'MYA',
  id: 149,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'yōon']
}, {
  front: 'りゃ',
  back: 'RYA',
  id: 150,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'yōon']
}, {
  front: 'きゅ',
  back: 'KYU',
  id: 151,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'yōon']
}, {
  front: 'しゅ',
  back: 'SHU',
  id: 151,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'yōon']
}, {
  front: 'ちゅ',
  back: 'CHU',
  id: 152,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'yōon']
}, {
  front: 'にゅ',
  back: 'NYU',
  id: 153,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'yōon']
}, {
  front: 'ひゅ',
  back: 'HYU',
  id: 154,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'yōon']
}, {
  front: 'みゅ',
  back: 'MYU',
  id: 155,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'yōon']
}, {
  front: 'りゅ',
  back: 'RYU',
  id: 156,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'yōon']
}, {
  front: 'きょ',
  back: 'KYO',
  id: 157,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'yōon']
}, {
  front: 'しょ',
  back: 'SHO',
  id: 158,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'yōon']
}, {
  front: 'ちょ',
  back: 'CHO',
  id: 159,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'yōon']
}, {
  front: 'にょ',
  back: 'NYO',
  id: 160,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'yōon']
}, {
  front: 'ひょ',
  back: 'HYO',
  id: 161,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'yōon']
}, {
  front: 'みょ',
  back: 'MYO',
  id: 162,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'yōon']
}, {
  front: 'りょ',
  back: 'RYO',
  id: 163,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'yōon']
}, {
  front: 'ぎゃ',
  back: 'GYA',
  id: 164,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'yōon', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'じゃ',
  back: 'JA',
  id: 165,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'yōon', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'ぢゃ',
  back: 'DJA',
  id: 166,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'yōon', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'びゃ',
  back: 'BYA',
  id: 167,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'yōon', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'ぴゃ',
  back: 'PYA',
  id: 168,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'yōon', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'ぎゅ',
  back: 'GYU',
  id: 169,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'yōon', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'じゅ',
  back: 'JU',
  id: 170,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'yōon', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'ぢゅ',
  back: 'DJU',
  id: 171,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'yōon', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'びゅ',
  back: 'BYU',
  id: 172,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'yōon', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'ぴゅ',
  back: 'PYU',
  id: 173,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'yōon', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'ぎょ',
  back: 'GYO',
  id: 174,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'yōon', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'じょ',
  back: 'JO',
  id: 175,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'yōon', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'ぢょ',
  back: 'DJO',
  id: 176,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'yōon', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'びょ',
  back: 'BYO',
  id: 177,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'yōon', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'ぴょ',
  back: 'PYO',
  id: 178,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['hiragana', 'yōon', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'キャ',
  back: 'KYA',
  id: 179,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'yōon']
}, {
  front: 'シャ',
  back: 'SHA',
  id: 180,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'yōon']
}, {
  front: 'シャ',
  back: 'CHA',
  id: 181,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'yōon']
}, {
  front: 'ニャ',
  back: 'NYA',
  id: 182,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'yōon']
}, {
  front: 'ヒャ',
  back: 'HYA',
  id: 183,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'yōon']
}, {
  front: 'ミャ',
  back: 'MYA',
  id: 184,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'yōon']
}, {
  front: 'リャ',
  back: 'RYA',
  id: 185,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'yōon']
}, {
  front: 'キュ',
  back: 'KYU',
  id: 186,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'yōon']
}, {
  front: 'シュ',
  back: 'SHU',
  id: 187,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'yōon']
}, {
  front: 'チュ',
  back: 'CHU',
  id: 188,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'yōon']
}, {
  front: 'ニュ',
  back: 'NYU',
  id: 189,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'yōon']
}, {
  front: 'ヒュ',
  back: 'HYU',
  id: 190,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'yōon']
}, {
  front: 'ミュ',
  back: 'MYU',
  id: 191,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'yōon']
}, {
  front: 'リュ',
  back: 'RYU',
  id: 192,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'yōon']
}, {
  front: 'キョ',
  back: 'KYO',
  id: 193,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'yōon']
}, {
  front: 'ショ',
  back: 'SHO',
  id: 194,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'yōon']
}, {
  front: 'チョ',
  back: 'CHO',
  id: 195,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'yōon']
}, {
  front: 'ニョ',
  back: 'NYO',
  id: 196,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'yōon']
}, {
  front: 'ヒョ',
  back: 'HYO',
  id: 197,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'yōon']
}, {
  front: 'ミョ',
  back: 'MYO',
  id: 198,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'yōon']
}, {
  front: 'リョ',
  back: 'RYO',
  id: 199,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'yōon']
}, {
  front: 'ギャ',
  back: 'GYA',
  id: 200,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'yōon', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'ジャ',
  back: 'JA',
  id: 201,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'yōon', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'ヂャ',
  back: 'DJA',
  id: 202,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'yōon', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'ビャ',
  back: 'BYA',
  id: 203,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'yōon', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'ピャ',
  back: 'PYA',
  id: 204,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'yōon', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'ギュ',
  back: 'GYU',
  id: 205,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'yōon', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'ジュ',
  back: 'JU',
  id: 206,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'yōon', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'ヂュ',
  back: 'DJU',
  id: 207,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'yōon', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'ビュ',
  back: 'BYU',
  id: 208,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'yōon', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'ピュ',
  back: 'PYU',
  id: 209,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'yōon', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'ギョ',
  back: 'GYO',
  id: 210,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'yōon', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'ジョ',
  back: 'JO',
  id: 211,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'yōon', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'ヂョ',
  back: 'DJO',
  id: 212,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'yōon', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'ビョ',
  back: 'BYO',
  id: 213,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'yōon', '(han)dakuten']
}, {
  front: 'ピョ',
  back: 'PYO',
  id: 214,
  difficulty: 1,
  tags: ['katakana', 'yōon', '(han)dakuten']
}];
export const difficulties = [{
  index: 1,
  name: 'easy',
  color: '#E8E8E8',
  textColor: '#686868'
}, {
  index: 2,
  name: 'normal',
  color: '#C0C0C0',
  textColor: 'white'
}, {
  index: 3,
  name: 'hard',
  color: '#989898',
  textColor: 'white'
}, {
  index: 4,
  name: 'impossible',
  color: '#686868',
  textColor: 'white'
}];
export const collection1 = {
  id: 1,
  type: 'collection',
  cards: [1, 2, 3]
};
export const exercise1 = {
  type: 'exercise',
  id: 1,
  name: 'Katakanas',
  urlName: 'katakanas',
  tag: 'katakana' // cards: [48, 49, 50, 51, 52, 53, 54, 55, 56, 57, 58, 59, 60, 61, 62, 63, 64, 65, 66, 67, 68, 69, 70, 71, 72, 73, 74, 75, 76, 77, 78, 79, 80, 81, 82, 83, 84, 85, 86, 87, 88, 89, 90, 91, 92, 93],

};
export const exercise2 = {
  type: 'exercise',
  id: 2,
  name: 'Hiraganas',
  urlName: 'hiraganas',
  tag: 'hiragana' // cards: [1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30, 31, 32, 33, 34, 35, 36, 37, 38, 39, 40, 41, 42, 43, 44, 45, 46, 47],

};